# FASICA ROBI

MULTIFACETED PROFESSIONAL WITH DIVERSE EXPERIENCE AND A PASSION FOR EXCELLENCE

# **PROFILE**

Versatile professional with over five years' experience working in fast-paced environments demanding strong organizational and technical abilities, and advanced interpersonal skills. Confident and poised in interactions with individuals at all levels. Detail-oriented, resourceful, and reliable; able to multi-task effectively and see projects through to completion.

# **SKILLS**

HTML/ CSS

JavaScript/jQuery
ApplyYourself
Banner
Bilingual
COGNOS
Collaboration
Data entry

Microsoft Office (Outlook, Excel, Powerpoint, Word setc)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Georgetown University School of Nursing and Health Studies, Program Coordinator | June 2018 - Present |

- •Maintain budget and track expenditures/transactions
- •Triage student and faculty needs/requests as they arise in person, by phone or by email; provide referral to appropriate resources or members of the administration and assist each individual with reaching a timely resolution.
- •Process all verification forms and enrollment letters for students
- •Assist in creating semester class schedules
- •Ensure technology is used correctly and functioning properly for all operations (video conferencing, presentations, Typhon (clinical placement online platform), Cognos, (2U) online classroom platform)
- •Review program logs to ensure total compliance with the latest CCNE standards and guidelines while taking care of discrepancies.
- •Comprehensive large-scale event planning: First & Second Year Orientations, Graduation, Pinning Ceremony, On-Campus Intensive)
- •Manage social media outlets for promotional and educational purposes

# Georgetown University Biomedical Graduate Education, Admissions Analyst | January 2018 – June 2018 Washington, DC

- •Examine academic records of students to determine eligibility of incoming students.
- •Receives, codes, verifies, and processes applications and related documents.
- •Studies course prerequisites, degree equivalents, and accreditation of schools, and computes grade point averages to establish student qualifications for admission.
- •Manages requests for assistance and trouble-shooting record issues.
- •Using the Graduate school codes, process decisions in BANNER. Generate and send out decision letters via ApplyYourself. Manage all admission queries in COGNOS/ApplyYourself.
- •First point of contact for potential graduate and PHD students..

# FASICA ROBI

MULTIFACETED PROFESSIONAL WITH DIVERSE EXPERIENCE AND A PASSION FOR EXCELLENCE

# HIGHLIGHTS

Performance Driven Sales
Experience Managerial
Experience Quickly
Promoted within
Organization
B.S. Degree

#### **EDUCATION**

George Washington University Coding Bootcamp Feburary 2021 - Present

Marymount University Bachelor of Science, Biology

# WORK EXPERIENCE (Continued)

#### Global Health College, Registrar December 2015 - December 2017 Alexandria, VA

Created, maintained, and audited student records in compliance with ACICS accreditation and internal regulations.

Improved method for storage of students' records. Configured reliable, inclusive student schedules to increase retention and prevent unnecessary drops.

Formulated curriculum outlines for first time students Scheduled 400+ students.

Assisted in transition from 16-Week class model to an 8- Week model. Provided database management for department, touch- tone and inperson registration, transcripts, and degree/ graduation audits.

#### Global Health College, Student Services Coordinator | September 2014-December 2015 Alexandria, VA

- •Advised and counseled prospective students.
- •Consistently met and exceeded recruiting goals.
- •Implemented strategies to increase program effectiveness. Hired, trained, supervised and evaluated work of receptionist.

# Marine Corps Scholarship Foundation, Operations Coordinator | January 2014-July 2014Alexandria, VA

- •Organized and managed fundraising events.
- •Updated and e-filed contracts and amendments.
- •Served as a liaison between employees, management, and scholarship recipients.
- •Conducted routine quality audits to ensure that work was progressing per specifications and initiated corrective action.